Luis Alejandro Campos Hernandez

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science



Personal Data

Luis Alejandro Campos Hernandez

dheboss7lol@gmail.com theboss7lol@gmail.com

. +58 4147666579

Cerca del terminal, por el hotel Monagas, Primer Callejón, La Murallita, CasaN°26

··· 13 /12/2001

് Man

Venezuela

路 Single

j github.com/RuisuCode

Languages

Spanish English



Hobbies

Develop Software

Develop Web Pages

Develop APIS

About Me

I am a person with both **academic and professional experience**, I have the time available both in **person and remotely**. I have ease of communication, both in Spanish and English (Technical), **i have worked in large and small teams on software development**. A pro-active person, **with time and dedication to learn new technologies and with excellent logic to adapt to new developments**, patient and dedicated.

Education

From 1st grade to 6th grade U.E.P Lino de las Mercedes del Valle, Maturín Sep 2006 - Jul 2013

From 1st to 5th year U.E.C.A. Dr. Braulio Pérez Marcío, Maturín Oct 2013 - Apr 2018

Specialized in natural sciences bachelor's degree

Systems engineering Apr 2018 - abr 2019 Instituto Universitario Politécnico "Santiago Mariño", Maturín

Computer Science Abr 2022 - Present

Universidad Bolivariana De Venezuela, Maturín

Specialized: Bachelor of Computer Science

Work Experience

Front-End React Web Developer Lotería de Oriente,Monagas-Maturín

Agu 2023 - Oct 2024

Back-End Web Developer AdonisJs (Node Js) Escuela Exp. Atletismo Monagas, Monagas-Maturín Dic 2023 - Oct 2024

Nov 2022

Courses

English certificate level A1 Nov 2021
English certificate level A1-A2 Feb 2022

PHP Introduction Certificate

Technologies

React
TypeScript
Node IS

HTML

CSS

Git(Gitlab & Github)

Python Adonis JS

